Contact

6368753950 (Home) liz.houck@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/liz-houck-bsn-rn-ccrn-b4410175 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Nursing
BLS
Critical Care

Liz Houck, BSN, RN, CCRN

Critical Care RN at SSM Health St. Louis

Greater St. Louis Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, Patient Education, Charge Nurse Responsibilities, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), and Intensive Care. Experience with IABP, and Impella devices. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Registered Nursing from University of Missouri-Saint Louis. Current CCRN, BLS and ACLS.

Experience

SSM Health St. Louis Critical Care RN January 2020 - Present (6 months)

The University of Texas Medical Branch 3 years 1 month

Critical Care Registered Nurse May 2019 - January 2020 (9 months) Webster, Texas

Registered Nurse

January 2017 - January 2020 (3 years 1 month)

United States

MICU/CCU

CHI St. Luke's Health Registered Nurse July 2016 - January 2017 (7 months) Houston, Texas Area

PACU

SSM Health Saint Louis University Hospital 3 years 1 month

CVICU RN, BSN

February 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 6 months)

CVICU

Impellas, IABP, Cardiology, Cardio Thoracic Surgery

Trauma/ Surgery RN
July 2013 - February 2015 (1 year 8 months)

Med/Surg with concentration in Trauma and post surgery patients

Education

University of Missouri-Saint Louis
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2013)